Vicki Goldberg Research Files
Vicki Goldberg Research Files
before 1992
Goldberg, Vicki.
24 linear ft.
Research files on American photography and photographers, including Margaret Bourke-White.
2750916
Biographical History
Vicki Goldberg is an American photography critic and author. Among her works is a biography of noted American photographer Margaret Bourke-White.
Scope and Contents of the Collection
The Vicki Goldberg Research Files consist of Goldberg's research files on American photography and photographers. Included in the collection are several boxes relating to noted photographer Margaret Bourke-White and a number of audiorecordings of interviews. An alphabetic index to the tapes is provided at the end of this finding aid.
Arrangement of the Collection
The collection is unprocessed and remains in original order.
Subject and Genre Headings
Biography; Photography; Bourke-White, Margaret, 1904-1971 -- Biography.; Goldberg, Vicki.; Photographers -- United States.; Photographic critics -- United States.; Photography -- United States.; Audiocassettes.; Research notes.; Sound recordings.; Biographers.
Access Restrictions
The majority of our archival and manuscript collections are housed offsite and require advanced notice for retrieval. Researchers are encouraged to contact us in advance concerning the collection material they wish to access for their research.
Access to recordings requires advance notice to produce a use copy.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Vicki Goldberg, 2000.
Inventory
- Interviews
  All interviews are audiorecordings, on cassette. Interviews are listed in order by Ms Goldberg's original identification number, starting with VG 001. An alphabetic index is provided at the end of this finding aid. Identification numbers assigned by are given in parentheses, e.g. "(ID# goldberg_v_001)".
  Access to recordings requires advance notice to produce a use copy.
  - VG 001 Ansel Adams 1 of 1, 09/02/1982; goldberg_v_001; 1 audio cassette (Box 1)
  - VG 002 Michael J. Arlen 2 of 2, 03/03/1982; goldberg_v_002; 1 audio cassette (Box 1)
  - VG 003 Eve Arnold 2 of 2, goldberg_v_003; mostly MBW; 1 audio cassette (Box 1)
  - VG 004 Hugo Block 2 Sides, 05/14/1982; goldberg_v_004; 1 audio cassette (Box 1)
  - VG 005 Sylvia Bothe 1 of 1, 02/06/1984; goldberg_v_005; phone interview; 1 audio cassette (Box 1)
  - VG 006 Margaret Bourke-White Interview, goldberg_v_006; 1 audio cassette (Box 1)
  - VG 007 MBW Town Hall Interview, 01/23/1953; goldberg_v_007; 1 audio cassette (Box 1)
  - VG 008 Bourke-White Talk, goldberg_v_008; 1 audio cassette (Box 1)
  - VG 009 Francis (Hank) Brennan 1 of 1, 07/26/1982; goldberg_v_009; 1 audio cassette (Box 1)
  - VG 010 John Bryson 2 of 2, 06/24/1983; goldberg_v_010; 1 audio cassette (Box 1)
  - VG 011 Erskine Caldwell 1 of 1, 12/02/1982; goldberg_v_011; 1 audio cassette (Box 1)
  - VG 011a Erskine Caldwell, 01/20/1983; goldberg_v_012; 1 audio cassette (Box 1)
  - VG 012 Cornell Capa (and also Ruth Lester), 02/04/1982; goldberg_v_013; 1 audio cassette (Box 1)
  - VG 013 Henry Cassidy 2 of 2, 01/10/1983; goldberg_v_014; 1 audio cassette (Box 1)
  - VG 014 John Chanberlain, 01/1983; goldberg_v_015; 1 audio cassette (Box 1)
  - VG 015 Noel Clark 1 of 1, 08/19/1982; goldberg_v_016; 1 audio cassette (Box 1)
  - VG 016 Dabney Caldwell Side 1 of 1, 05/14/1982; goldberg_v_017; 1 audio cassette (Box 1)
  - VG 017 Side 1 R. H. Connolly interview Florence and Joe C. Re: Goldberg letter, 01/23/1982; goldberg_v_018; 1 audio cassette (Box 1)
  - VG 018 David Cort 2 of 2, 10/26/1982; goldberg_v_019; 1 audio cassette (Box 1)
  - VG 019 Harold Costain 1 of 1, 02/06/1984; goldberg_v_020; phone interview; 1 audio cassette (Box 1)
  - VG 020 Norman Cousins 1 and 2 of 3, 04/16/1982; goldberg_v_021; 1 audio cassette (Box 1)
  - VG 021 Norman Cousins and Ellen Cousins Side 3 of 3, 04/17/1982; goldberg_v_022; 1 audio cassette (Box 1)
  - VG 022 Kathryn Cravens 1 of 1, 12/07/1983; goldberg_v_023; phone interview; 1 audio cassette (Box 1)
  - VG 023 Betty Cronander Tape 1 of 3, 01/17/1980; goldberg_v_024; 1 audio cassette (Box 1)
  - VG 024 Betty Cronander 2nd Tape, 01/17/1983; goldberg_v_025; 1 audio cassette (Box 1)
  - VG 025 Betty Cronander 3rd of tape 3, 01/17/1983; goldberg_v_026; 1 audio cassette (Box 1)
  - VG 026 Edward P. Curtis 1 of 1, 05/11/1984; goldberg_v_027; 1 audio cassette (Box 1)
  - VG 028 Helen Caldwell Cushman 1st of 2 tapes, 01/20/1983; goldberg_v_028; 1 audio cassette (Box 1)
  - VG 028 Helen Cushman 2nd tape, 01/20/1983; goldberg_v_029; 1 audio cassette (Box 1)
  - VG 029 Roselle Davis, 02/28/1983; goldberg_v_030; 1 audio cassette (Box 1)
  - VG 030 Max Desfers 1 of 1, 07/25/1983; goldberg_v_031; 1 audio cassette (Box 1)
  - VG 031 Maitland Edey 2 of 2, 12/31/1982; goldberg_v_032; 1 audio cassette (Box 1)
  - VG 032 Eisenstadt, 01/22/1982; goldberg_v_033; 1 audio cassette (Box 1)
  - VG 033 Robert Elson 2 of 2, 08/02/1982; goldberg_v_034; 1 audio cassette (Box 1)
  - VG 034 Walter Engel 1 of 1, 08/22/1983; goldberg_v_035; 1 audio cassette (Box 1)
  - VG 035 JR Eyerman, 01/21/1983; goldberg_v_036; 1 audio cassette (Box 1)
  - VG 035a JR Eyerman 2nd tape of 2, 01/21/1983; goldberg_v_037; 1 audio cassette (Box 1)
  - VG 036 Eyes on Russia MBW Audio of Film Side 1 of 1, goldberg_v_038; 1 audio cassette (Box 1)
  - VG 037 Richard Fatherley 1 of 1, goldberg_v_039; 1 audio cassette (Box 1)
  - VG 038 Robert E. Fatherley and Wife 2 of 2, 12/13/1982; goldberg_v_040; 1 audio cassette (Box 1)
  - VG 039 Bob Fatherley 1 of 1, 05/03/1983; goldberg_v_041; 1 audio cassette (Box 1)
  - VG 040 Clay Felker, 02/07/1982; goldberg_v_042; 1 audio cassette (Box 2)
  - VG 041 Pel Pollard Finn side 1 of 2, 05/31/1982; goldberg_v_043; 1 audio cassette (Box 2)
  - VG 042 Alan Fisher 1 of 1, 08/22/1983; goldberg_v_044; phone interview; 1 audio cassette (Box 2)
  - VG 043 Harvey V. Fondiller, 04/06/1983; goldberg_v_045; 1 audio cassette (Box 2)
  - VG 044 For Women Only Part 1 WSTC Lillian Orman, 05/10/1963; goldberg_v_046; 1 audio cassette (Box 2)
  - VG 045 Barrett Gallagher, 09/13/1982; goldberg_v_047; 1 audio cassette (Box 2)
  - VG 046 Violette Gilfillian, 04/27/1983; goldberg_v_048; 1 audio cassette (Box 2)
  - VG 047 Jean Snow Gold, 08/28/1982; goldberg_v_049; 1 audio cassette (Box 2)
  - VG 048 Janet Gooding, 05/19/1983; goldberg_v_050; 1 audio cassette (Box 2)
  - VG 049 Ed. White; Felicia Gossman; Muriel White, goldberg_v_051; 1 audio cassette (Box 2)
  - VG 050 Ed. White; Felicia Gossman; Muriel White, 01/20/1983; goldberg_v_052; 1 audio cassette (Box 2)
  - VG 051 Edw. White, Felicia Gossman, Muriel White, goldberg_v_053; 1 audio cassette (Box 2)
  - VG 052 Manfred Gottfried, 08/16/1982; goldberg_v_054; 1 audio cassette (Box 2)
  - VG 053 Kenneth Gouldthorpe, 11/23/1982; goldberg_v_055; 1 audio cassette (Box 2)
  - VG 054 Mrs. Oscar Granbner, 05/13/1982; goldberg_v_056; 1 audio cassette (Box 2)
  - VG 055 Ralph Graves, 02/24/1982; goldberg_v_057; 1 audio cassette (Box 2)
  - VG 056 Allen Grover Sides 1 and 2 of 2, 05/04/1982; goldberg_v_058; 1 audio cassette (Box 2)
  - VG 057 Irving Haberman, 05/26/1983; goldberg_v_059; 1 audio cassette (Box 2)
  - VG 058 Jerry Hannafin, 12/21/1982; goldberg_v_060; 1 audio cassette (Box 2)
  - VG 059 Richards Eads Harrison, 05/07/1982; goldberg_v_061; 1 audio cassette (Box 2)
  - VG 061 Bernard Hayden, 06/29/1982; goldberg_v_062; 1 audio cassette (Box 2)
  - VG 062 Andrew Heiskell, 06/23/1982; goldberg_v_063; 1 audio cassette (Box 2)
  - VG 063 Don Hershey, goldberg_v_064; 1 audio cassette (Box 2)
  - VG 064 Eleanor Tracy Hodgins, 05/13/1982; goldberg_v_065; 1 audio cassette (Box 2)
  - VG 065 Ralph Ingersoll Side 4, 05/17/1982; goldberg_v_066; 1 audio cassette (Box 2)
  - VG 066 Ralph Ingersoll Sides 2 and 3, 05/17/1982; goldberg_v_067; 1 audio cassette (Box 2)
  - VG 067 Ralph Ingersoll Side 1, 05/17/1982; goldberg_v_068; 1 audio cassette (Box 2)
  - VG 068 Mrs. Charles Jacobson, 03/01/1982; goldberg_v_069; 1 audio cassette (Box 2)
  - VG 069 Sid James, 10/15/1982; goldberg_v_070; 1 audio cassette (Box 2)
  - VG 070 Dr. Edgar Kahn, 07/29/1982; goldberg_v_071; 1 audio cassette (Box 2)
  - VG 071 George Karas, 01/21/1982; goldberg_v_072; 1 audio cassette (Box 2)
  - VG 072 Joe Kaster Sides 1 and 2 of 3, 02/23/1982; goldberg_v_073; 1 audio cassette (Box 2)
  - VG 073 Joe Kaster Side 3 of 3, 02/23/1982; goldberg_v_074; 1 audio cassette (Box 2)
  - VG 074 Peter Keane Sides 1 and 2, 04/16/1982; goldberg_v_075; 1 audio cassette (Box 2)
  - VG 075 Percy Knauth Sides 1 and 2 of 6, 04/14/1982; goldberg_v_076; 1 audio cassette (Box 2)
  - VG 076 Percy Knauth Sides 3 and 4, goldberg_v_077; 1 audio cassette (Box 2)
  - VG 077 Percy Knauth Sides 5 and 6 of 6, 04/14/1982; goldberg_v_078; 1 audio cassette (Box 2)
  - VG 078 Dr. Arthur Korf, 10/18/1982; goldberg_v_079; 1 audio cassette (Box 2)
  - VG 078a Dr. Arthur Korf, 11/02/1982; goldberg_v_080; 1 audio cassette (Box 2)
  - VG 079 Syracuse AV Lab MBW Korea notebooks, goldberg_v_081; 1 audio cassette (Box 2)
  - VG 080 LA Fri mng, 05/14/1943; goldberg_v_082; 1 audio cassette (Box 2)
  - VG 081 John La Montaine, 11/23/1982; goldberg_v_083; 1 audio cassette (Box 2)
  - VG 082 Clare Leighton, 11/29/1983; goldberg_v_084; 1 audio cassette (Box 3)
  - VG 083 Bill Leonard, 04/05/1984; goldberg_v_085; 1 audio cassette (Box 3)
  - VG 084 Max Lemer and Edna Lemer, 03/04/1984; goldberg_v_086; 1 audio cassette (Box 3)
  - VG 086 Alfred de Liagre Jr., goldberg_v_087; 1 audio cassette (Box 3)
  - VG 087 Maxim Lieber, 03/31/1982; goldberg_v_088; 1 audio cassette (Box 3)
  - VG 088 Joseph Liss, 08/08/1982; goldberg_v_089; 1 audio cassette (Box 3)
  - VG 089 Joseph Liss; Magaret Bourke-White Interview, goldberg_v_090; 1 audio cassette (Box 3)
  - VG 090 John Loengard, goldberg_v_091; 1 audio cassette (Box 3)
  - VG 091 Stefan Lorant, 07/26/1983; goldberg_v_092; 1 audio cassette (Box 3)
  - VG 092 Dwight Macdonald, 03/1982; goldberg_v_093; 1 audio cassette (Box 3)
  - VG 093 Elizabeth Magnuson, 10/17/1982; goldberg_v_094; 1 audio cassette (Box 3)
  - VG 094 Interview was This is NY w. Mrs. Magnuson, 08/26/1957; goldberg_v_095; 1 audio cassette (Box 3)
  - VG 095 Tom Maloney, goldberg_v_096; 1 audio cassette (Box 3)
  - VG 096 Tom Maloney Side 3, 03/30/1982; goldberg_v_097; 1 audio cassette (Box 3)
  - VG 097 Dr. Morton Marks, 11/18/1982; goldberg_v_098; 1 audio cassette (Box 3)
  - VG 098 Tex McCrary, 05/10/1982; goldberg_v_099; 1 audio cassette (Box 3)
  - VG 099 Herb Mitang, 08/11/1982; goldberg_v_100; 1 audio cassette (Box 3)
  - VG 100 Hugh Moffett Side 1 and 2, goldberg_v_101; 1 audio cassette (Box 3)
  - VG 101 Hugh Moffett Side 3 and 4, goldberg_v_102; 1 audio cassette (Box 3)
  - VG 102 Interview w/ Mom and Dad, goldberg_v_103; 1 audio cassette (Box 3)
  - VG 103 AD and Jo Moore, 08/24/1983; goldberg_v_104; 1 audio cassette (Box 3)
  - VG 105 Myrle Morgan Side 1 and 2, 04/19/1982; goldberg_v_105; 1 audio cassette (Box 3)
  - VG 105a Myrle Morgan Side 3, 04/19/1982; goldberg_v_106; 1 audio cassette (Box 3)
  - VG 106 Barbara Morgan, 07/22/1982; goldberg_v_107; 1 audio cassette (Box 3)
  - VG 107 Mary Morris (Lawrence), 03/04/1984; goldberg_v_108; 1 audio cassette (Box 3)
  - VG 108 John Morris Side 1 and 2, 07/12/1982; goldberg_v_109; 1 audio cassette (Box 3)
  - VG 109 John Morris Side 3, goldberg_v_110; 1 audio cassette (Box 3)
  - VG 110 Ralph Morse, 02/15/1982; goldberg_v_111; 1 audio cassette (Box 3)
  - VG 111 Duplicate Ed Murrow Show 1955, goldberg_v_112; 1 audio cassette (Box 3)
  - VG 112 Ed Murrow Interview, goldberg_v_113; 1 audio cassette (Box 3)
  - VG 113 Janet Murrow, 09/26/1982; goldberg_v_114; 1 audio cassette (Box 3)
  - VG 114 Shelley Mydans and Frank White, goldberg_v_115; 1 audio cassette (Box 3)
  - VG 115 Carl Mydans Side 1 and 2, goldberg_v_116; 1 audio cassette (Box 3)
  - VG 115a Carl Mydans Side 3 and 4, goldberg_v_117; 1 audio cassette (Box 3)
  - VG 116 Beaumont Newhall, 09/11/1982; goldberg_v_118; 1 audio cassette (Box 3)
  - VG 117 Clara Nicolai, 05/29/1984; goldberg_v_119; 1 audio cassette (Box 3)
  - VG 118 Doris O’Weil, 02/24/1982; goldberg_v_120; 1 audio cassette (Box 3)
  - VG 119 Evelyn Openhym Side 1 of 2, 03/15/1982; goldberg_v_121; 1 audio cassette (Box 3)
  - VG 120 Herb Orth, George Karas, 01/21/1982; goldberg_v_122; 1 audio cassette (Box 3)
  - VG 121 George Karas, Herb Orth, 01/28/1982; goldberg_v_123; 1 audio cassette (Box 3)
  - VG 122 Myrna Papurt Weibel, 04/14/1983; goldberg_v_124; 1 audio cassette (Box 3)
  - VG 123 Gordon Parks, 03/25/1982; goldberg_v_125; 1 audio cassette (Box 3)
  - VG 124 Col. Roswell Perry, 08/02/1983; goldberg_v_126; 1 audio cassette (Box 4)
  - VG 125 John Phillips (1 and 2 of 4), 02/25/1982; goldberg_v_127; 1 audio cassette (Box 4)
  - VG 126 John Phillips (3 and 4 of 4), 02/25/1982; goldberg_v_128; 1 audio cassette (Box 4)
  - VG 127 Gerard Piel, 07/06/1983; goldberg_v_129; 1 audio cassette (Box 4)
  - VG 128 Harriet Pilpel, 05/18/1982; goldberg_v_130; 1 audio cassette (Box 4)
  - VG 129 David Richardson, goldberg_v_131; 1 audio cassette (Box 4)
  - VG 130 Robert Yarnall Richie, 01/03/1983; goldberg_v_132; 1 audio cassette (Box 4)
  - VG 131 Roger, 12/06/1981; goldberg_v_133; 1 audio cassette (Box 4)
  - VG 132 Roger, 12/07/1981; goldberg_v_134; 1 audio cassette (Box 4)
  - VG 133 Roger Side 3, goldberg_v_135; 1 audio cassette (Box 4)
  - VG 134 Arthur Rothstein, 05/04/1983; goldberg_v_136; 1 audio cassette (Box 4)
  - VG 135 Roy Rowan, 06/16/1983; goldberg_v_137; 1 audio cassette (Box 4)
  - VG 136 Dr. Howard Rusk, goldberg_v_138; 1 audio cassette (Box 4)
  - VG 137 Libby Sachar, 05/11/1982; goldberg_v_139; 1 audio cassette (Box 4)
  - VG 138 Eleanor and Daniel Saidenberg, 04/02/1984; goldberg_v_140; 1 audio cassette (Box 4)
  - VG 139 George Sambrus, 04/08/1984; goldberg_v_141; 1 audio cassette (Box 4)
  - VG 140 Margaret Smith Sargent Sides 1 and 2 out of 5, 02/10/1982; goldberg_v_142; 1 audio cassette (Box 4)
  - VG 141 Margaret Smith Sargent Sides 3 and 4, 02/10/1982; goldberg_v_143; 1 audio cassette (Box 4)
  - VG 142 Margaret Smith Sargent Side 5, 02/10/1982; goldberg_v_144; 1 audio cassette (Box 4)
  - VG 143 Shigero Sasamori, 01/21/1983; goldberg_v_145; 1 audio cassette (Box 4)
  - VG 144 David Scherman, goldberg_v_146; 1 audio cassette (Box 4)
  - VG 145 [No Title], goldberg_v_147; 1 audio cassette (Box 4)
  - VG 146 Max Robert Schrayer, 04/22/1982; goldberg_v_148; 1 audio cassette (Box 4)
  - VG 147 Lee Scott, 07/29/1982; goldberg_v_149; 1 audio cassette (Box 4)
  - VG 148 Sean Side 1 and 2 of 4, 01/14/1982; goldberg_v_150; 1 audio cassette (Box 4)
  - VG 148a Sean Side 3, 01/15/1982; goldberg_v_151; 1 audio cassette (Box 4)
  - VG 149 Dottie Seiberling, 01/25/1982; goldberg_v_152; 1 audio cassette (Box 4)
  - VG 150 Robert Sherrod, 09/17/1982; goldberg_v_153; 1 audio cassette (Box 4)
  - VG 151 Andrea Simon, 08/26/1982; goldberg_v_154; 1 audio cassette (Box 4)
  - VG 152 Father Daniel Shehan, 06/07/1983; goldberg_v_155; 1 audio cassette (Box 4)
  - VG 153 Father Shehan and Father Linehan, goldberg_v_156; 1 audio cassette (Box 4)
  - VG 154 Father Shehan (James) and Father Daniel Linehan, 06/07/1983; goldberg_v_157; 1 audio cassette (Box 4)
  - VG 155 Bradley Smith, 09/07/1984; goldberg_v_158; 1 audio cassette (Box 4)
  - VG 156 Wilma Smitheland, 03/11/1984; goldberg_v_159; 1 audio cassette (Box 4)
  - VG 157 Col. Craig Smyser, 08/30/1985; goldberg_v_160; 1 audio cassette (Box 4)
  - VG 158 Howard Sochurek, 06/25/1984; goldberg_v_161; 1 audio cassette (Box 4)
  - VG 159 Edward Stanley 1 of 4, 03/08/1982; goldberg_v_162; 1 audio cassette (Box 4)
  - VG 160 Edward Stanley 2nd tape, goldberg_v_163; 1 audio cassette (Box 4)
  - VG 161 Ralph Steiner, 04/28/1982; goldberg_v_164; 1 audio cassette (Box 4)
  - VG 162 Ralph Steiner duplicate, goldberg_v_165; 1 audio cassette (Box 4)
  - VG 163 Hedda Steme, goldberg_v_166; 1 audio cassette (Box 4)
  - VG 164 Michael J. Strok, goldberg_v_167; 1 audio cassette (Box 4)
  - VG 165 William Sumits, goldberg_v_168; 1 audio cassette (Box 5)
  - VG 166 Tape 1, goldberg_v_169; 1 audio cassette (Box 5)
  - VG 167 Tape 2 Side 1, goldberg_v_170; 1 audio cassette (Box 5)
  - VG 168 Tape 3, goldberg_v_171; 1 audio cassette (Box 5)
  - VG 169 Tape 4, goldberg_v_172; 1 audio cassette (Box 5)
  - VG 170 Tape 5, goldberg_v_173; 1 audio cassette (Box 5)
  - VG 171 Joseph Thorndike, 08/03/1982; goldberg_v_174; 1 audio cassette (Box 5)
  - VG 172 Joseph Thorndike 2 of 2, 12/10/1982; goldberg_v_175; 1 audio cassette (Box 5)
  - VG 173 Joan Tower, 03/26/1984; goldberg_v_176; 1 audio cassette (Box 5)
  - VG 194 Teresa Wright, 05/19/1983; goldberg_v_177; 1 audio cassette (Box 5)
  - VG 175 Karen Tuttle, 12/20/1982; goldberg_v_178; 1 audio cassette (Box 5)
  - VG 176 John Vance, 07/15/1982; goldberg_v_179; 1 audio cassette (Box 5)
  - VG 177 John Vassos, 03/06/1982; goldberg_v_180; 1 audio cassette (Box 5)
  - VG 178 Eli Wallach, 04/29/1983; goldberg_v_181; 1 audio cassette (Box 5)
  - VG 179 William Walton, 11/11/1982; goldberg_v_182; 1 audio cassette (Box 5)
  - VG 180 Don Weadon, 11/16/1983; goldberg_v_183; 1 audio cassette (Box 5)
  - VG 181 Robert Weinstein 2 of 3 Sides, 01/19/1983; goldberg_v_184; 1 audio cassette (Box 5)
  - VG 182 Robert Weinstein, goldberg_v_185; 1 audio cassette (Box 5)
  - VG 183 Julius Weiss, 08/12/1982; goldberg_v_186; 1 audio cassette (Box 5)
  - VG 184 Joe Wershbar, 08/24/1982; goldberg_v_187; 1 audio cassette (Box 5)
  - VG 185 Lael Wertenbaker, goldberg_v_188; 1 audio cassette (Box 5)
  - VG 187 Mike White, 12/08/1981; goldberg_v_189; 1 audio cassette (Box 5)
  - VG 188 Mike White 3rd side, 12/08/1981; goldberg_v_190; 1 audio cassette (Box 5)
  - VG 189 Mike White Side 5, 12/08/1981; goldberg_v_191; 1 audio cassette (Box 5)
  - VG 190 Mike White Side 7, 12/08/1981; goldberg_v_192; 1 audio cassette (Box 5)
  - VG 191 Barbara Wild, 05/11/1982; goldberg_v_193; 1 audio cassette (Box 5)
  - VG 192 Lee Witkin, 12/22/1982; goldberg_v_194; 1 audio cassette (Box 5)
  - VG 193 Interview at WOW Omaha WBC Ref Recording, 02/22/1954; goldberg_v_195; 1 audio cassette (Box 5)
  - VG 195 Yale Joel, 07/07/1983; goldberg_v_196; 1 audio cassette (Box 5)
  - VG 196 B[o]urke-White, goldberg_v_197; 1 audio cassette (Box 5)
  - VG 197 Betty Cronander 2 of 2, goldberg_v_198; 1 audio cassette (Box 5)
  - VG 198 Charles Rotkin, goldberg_v_199; 1 audio cassette (Box 5)
- Research files
  This part of the collection is unprocessed and is not accessible at this time.
Alphabetical index to tapes
"LA Fri mng" VG 080
"Mom and Dad" VG 102
----, RogerVG 131 VG 132 VG 133
----, SeanVG 148 VG 148a
[unidentified interview], WOW Omaha VG 193
[untitled] VG 145
[untitled] Tape 1 VG 166
[untitled] Tape 2 VG 167
[untitled] Tape 3 VG 168
[untitled] Tape 4 VG 169
[untitled] Tape 5 VG 170
Adams, Ansel VG 001
Arlen, Michael J. VG 002
Arnold, Eve VG 003
Block, Hugo VG 004
Bothe, Sylvia VG 005
Bourke-White, MargaretVG 006 VG 007 VG 008 VG 036 VG 079 VG 089 VG 196
Brennan, Francis (Hank) VG 009
Bryson, John VG 010
C---, Florence and Joe VG 017
Caldwell, Dabney VG 016
Caldwell, ErskineVG 011 VG 011a
Caldwell, Helen Cushman VG 028
Capa, Cornell VG 012
Cassidy, Henry VG 013
Chanberlain, John VG 014
Clark, Noel VG 015
Connolly, R. H. VG 017
Cort, David VG 018
Costain, Harold VG 019
Cousins, Ellen VG 021
Cousins, NormanVG 020 VG 021
Cravens, Kathryn VG 022
Cronander, BettyVG 023 VG 024 VG 025 VG 197
Curtis, Edward P. VG 026
Cushman, Helen VG 028
Davis, Roselle VG 029
de Liagre, Alfred Jr. VG 086
Desfers, Max VG 030
Eads, Richard Harrison VG 059
Edey, Maitland VG 031
Eisenstadt, Sergei VG 032
Elson, Robert VG 033
Engel, Walter VG 034
Eyerman, J. R.VG 035 VG 035a
Eyes on Russia VG 036
Fatherley, Bob VG 039
Fatherley, Richard VG 037
Fatherley, Robert E. and Mrs. VG 038
Felker, Clay VG 040
Finn, Pel Pollard VG 041
Fisher, Alan VG 042
Fondiller, Harvey V. VG 043
For Women Only (Lillian Orman) VG 044
Gallagher, Barrett VG 045
Gilfillian, Violette VG 046
Gooding, Janet VG 048
Gossman, FeliciaVG 049 VG 050 VG 051
Gottfried, Manfred VG 052
Gouldthorpe, Kenneth VG 053
Granbner, Mrs. Oscar VG 054
Graves, Ralph VG 055
Grover, Allen VG 056
Haberman, Irving VG 057
Hannafin, Jerry VG 058
Hayden, Bernard VG 061
Heiskell, Andrew VG 062
Hershey, Don VG 063
Ingersoll, RalphVG 065 VG 066 VG 067
Jacobson, Mrs. Charles VG 068
James, Sid VG 069
Joel, Yale VG 195
Kahn, Edgar (Dr.) VG 070
Karas, GeorgeVG 071 VG 120 VG 121
Kaster, JoeVG 072 VG 073
Keane, Peter VG 074
Knauth, PercyVG 075 VG 076 VG 077
Korf, Arthur (Dr.)VG 078 VG 078a
La Montaine, John VG 081
Leighton, Clare VG 082
Leonard, Bill VG 083
Lerner, Max and Edna VG 084
Lester, Ruth VG 012
Lieber, Maxim VG 087
Linehan, Father DanielVG 153 VG 153 VG 154
Liss, JosephVG 088 VG 089
Loengard, John VG 090
Lorant, Stefan VG 091
Macdonald, Dwight VG 092
Magnuson, ElizabethVG 093 VG 094
Maloney, TomVG 095 VG 096
Marks, Morton (Dr.) VG 097
McCrary, Tex VG 098
Mitang, Herb VG 099
Moffett, HughVG 100 VG 101
Moore, A. D. and Jo VG 103
Morgan, Barbara VG 106
Morgan, MyrleVG 105 VG 105a
Morris, JohnVG 108 VG 109
Morris, Mary (Lawrence) VG 107
Morse, Ralph VG 110
Murrow, EdVG 111 VG 112
Murrow, Janet VG 113
Mydans, CarlVG 115 VG 115a
Mydans, Shelley VG 114
Newhall, Beaumont VG 116
Nicolai, Clara VG 117
O’Weil, Doris VG 118
Openhym, Evelyn VG 119
Orman, Lillian VG 044
Orth, HerbVG 120 VG 121
Papurt, Myrna Weibel VG 122
Parks, Gordon VG 123
Perry, Roswell (Col.) VG 124
Phillips, JohnVG 125 VG 126
Piel, Gerard VG 127
Pilpel, Harriet VG 128
Richardson, David VG 129
Robert, Max Schrayer VG 146
Rothstein, Arthur VG 134
Rotkin, Charles VG 198
Rowan, Roy VG 135
Rusk, Howard (Dr.) VG 136
Sachar, Libby VG 137
Saidenberg, Eleanor and Daniel VG 138
Sambrus, George VG 139
Sasamori, Shigero VG 143
Scherman, David VG 144
Scott, Lee VG 147
Seiberling, Dottie VG 149
Shehan, Father JamesVG 152 VG 154
Sherrod, Robert VG 150
Simon, Andrea VG 151
Smith, Bradley VG 155
Smith, Margaret SargentVG 140 VG 141 VG 142
Smitheland, Wilma VG 156
Smyser, Craig (Col.) VG 157
Snow, Jean Gold VG 047
Sochurek, Howard VG 158
Stanley, EdwardVG 159 VG 160
Steiner, RalphVG 161 VG 162
Steme, Hedda VG 163
Strok, Michael J. VG 164
Sumits, William VG 165
Syracuse AV Lab (MBW Korea notebooks) VG 079
This is New York (Elizabeth Magnuson) VG 094
Thorndike, JosephVG 171 VG 172
Tower, Joan VG 173
Tracy, Eleanor Hodgins VG 064
Tuttle, Karen VG 175
Vance, John VG 176
Vassos, John VG 177
Wallach, Eli VG 178
Walton, William VG 179
Weadon, Don VG 180
Weinstein, RobertVG 181 VG 182
Weiss, Julius VG 183
Wershbar, Joe VG 184
Wertenbaker, Lael VG 185
White, EdVG 049 VG 050 VG 051
White, Frank VG 114
White, MikeVG 187 VG 188 VG 189 VG 190
White, MurielVG 049 VG 050 VG 051
Wild, Barbara VG 191
Witkin, Lee VG 192
Wright, Teresa VG 194
Yarnall, Robert Richie VG 130